swissmine.club 2018-09-05

# Privacy Policy | Ducatus Network

Centurion Global Limited operates https://network.ducatus.net (the “Site”). This informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site. We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. You understand and agree that this may involve the transmission and storage of your personal data outside the country in which you live or of which you are a passport holder.

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name, gender, age, date of birth, address, nationality and one or more email addresses (“Personal Information”).

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. We may use this information to monitor server errors, server administration or to monitor visitor behaviour. It is not possible for this to be disabled on a per-user basis so you must leave this website (and the internet entirely) if you do not agree to this happening.

We may also use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information. We will give you the chance to refuse any marketing email from us in the future.

The security of your Personal Information is important to us but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date shown above and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

 **Statement** **concerning the use of cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier and are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Like many sites, we use cookies to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

Some cookies used on this website collect information about how visitors use a website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor.  All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how our website works.

Some cookies used on this website allow the website to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features.  These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customise. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting or providing feedback. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites. Cookies may also be used to improve the user experience and to enable some of the functionality provided by this website.

Please note that some cookies may be placed by third party service providers who perform some of these functions (or other services) for us.   Some of these services may be used to track your behaviour on other websites and we have no control over this.

By continuing to use this website without adjusting your browser’s cookie settings, you agree that we can place these cookies on your device.
